Su Krank
Krank
Scott hey
hahaha
ran
Hi, Scott!
Hi!
I'm Hikaru Morita from Sakurazaka Otisix
I'm Rina Inamura.
This is a capsule toy store.
Here we are!
Wow, the amount of toys is amazing!
Capsule toys...
I've been there once before.
Oh, you mentioned it, right?
But, you know, I did a presentation once.
I'd like to tell you about my usual capsule toy life.
I'd like to share my capsule toy life with you.
Capsule toy life?
It's part of my life.
Yes, yes, yes.
We did it once, together.
You gave me some recommendations.
I like it a lot. I watch it too.
So, are you having a good day?
I was really looking forward to it.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
Do you have a favorite series?
No, but I think I'm more of an animal person.
Are you getting these?
Yeah, like this.
You do it with this?
Sometimes I do it alone.
Wow, a Madori key chain.
This is nice.
I like the college kids' room.
I have a singer's room.
Singer? Madori?
What are you after, by the way?
Oh, you know, a secret room.
There's also a room for okedashi comedians.
I'll be there.
Here you go.
Let's go.
Mmm.
Mm-mm.
Oh, my God.
It's got tape on it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
There's tape on it.
I dared to do that kind of blah, blah, blah.
It's the first time.
It's the first time, so I thought I'd do one blur.
I see.
For real? For real?
Shall I open it?
Can you do me a favor?
It's open.
Oh, my God.
You're a pro!
What is it?
Oh, you're a famous actor.
He's a great actor. He's a great actor.
Look close.
He's got a pool in the back.
It's amazing.
Luna, you want to do this? This one.
Let's do it.
Here we go.
We have the tape.
I've got it. Be careful.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Concrete.
Alien room.
It's huge.
There's a lab and a comms room.
Alien room.Alien Room
I don't know.
Look at this. Food.
It's so cute.
They're food samples.
Wow, wow, wow. Yoshinoya.
That's amazing!
It's only 500 yen. You can buy it.
You could really buy a beef bowl.
You could put a ring or something on it.
That's nice. You wanna do something?
He likes you.
That kind of thing.
It's kind of a dad gag.
Isn't that too much?
Like the shampoo hat.
I like you. 300 yen.
I'll go.
Three.
Three? That's a lot of eggs in a popular series.
I like you?
Cute!
Chick Brothers.
I like chick brothers.
I'm a chick bro. I'm not a chick.
I want a chick bro.
Pink gold.
Pink gold means they're coming.
Oh, my God!
Here they are! Chick brothers!
Yay! You're late!
Taro Patience. I miss it.
I used to watch it.
Ocharumaru?
Good luck. I want to do this.
Pokemon!
This is a Pogeta Chance. Can I go now?
Which one's Pogeta?
This one.
The red one?
It's a Pokemon on fire.
Let's see if it works.
Please do.
I'd be happy to see anyone.
I don't even know if they're out.
Come on, new kids!
Crash.
How do you know?
He's right here.
On the porch.
It's nice.
I thought you could use it for makeup and stuff.
Sure, eye drops, stuff like that.
This is cute.
I'll use it.
It's totally fine until we get Pokemon.
You'll do Renu, right? You usually do.
I'll do it.
Please do.
Good night.
Okay, okay, okay.
What's that? What is that?
Pikachu!
He's so cute! Look! He's sleeping!
He's so cute!
Can I do it again?
Yeah!
Let's go!
It's really just like this, usually, until they fall asleep.
How many times have we done this? The same one.
I've done it like 20 times.
I've finally gotten the one I wanted, like, 20 times.
I see.
I almost cried.
It's like she's always been there.
That's so true.I really do.
Please.
Hogeta, please.
Hey! Hey!
Hogeta's here!
Red! Red!
Hogeta's here! Hey, guys!
And it's a tote bag! It's the size of a tote bag.
It's definitely bigger than the other one.
It's so cute!
It's a hogeta!
Is it open?
Oh, that's so cute!
That's called a hogeta.
Cute!
So cute!
Here, that's a cherry over there.
I think I'll put it in here.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Hogeta get!
Hogeta getta getta!
I got it!
Oh, it's Onpo!
Oh, Onpo!
I got it!
We got it!
Yumi-nee-no-san is on the show!
She's a regular on "Newly Selected".
She's on Wednesdays.
Oh, you're doing this?
Oh, I can swing it!
Lass 1?
Lappy's a big hit!
What the hell was lappy doing in there?
Rappy the Fury.
Rappy the Raging Lappy.
He's so cute when he's mad.
I'll put this on.
Oh, there it is!
Here it is! Here it is!
There it is.
Oh, yeah.
I like it.
You like it?
Can I try?
Sure, go ahead.
Let's see what you've got.
I'm still your idol.
Please do.
Give me a big smile.
Smile.
Wait a minute, I just laughed.
I'll do it too, right?
Of course, in that situation.
Not at all.
When it comes to doing it, I'd prefer a pointing hand, wouldn't you?
Isn't that a bit of a low bar?
It's like a request, but in a different way.
I want her to do it.
I'm begging you.
I want something good to come out of it.
What?
What did you get?
I got a good one.
Tell me you love me.
Can I ask you for a favor?
Shall we do it?
Yes, please.
I love it.
I love it. I want all the members to do this.
I want them to do it.
I'm sure.
Oh, it's so cute.
It's cute.
Oh, it's nice.
You can have fun, too.
You can have fun with your friends,
Have them fight with each other,
And make it awkward.
What is this?What's this?
I've never seen anything like it.
It's amazing. I don't know what happened.
Have you ever seen this before?
No, I haven't.
This one is 200 yen,
This one is 300 yen.
There is a difference.
It's true.
I'm curious about this.
I'm curious.
You want to go?
I want to.
What kind of stuff did you do?
Oh, there it is.
What?
What's this...
What is it?
It's a mischievous friend.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm Fukurin.
Fukubayashi of the mischievous friends.
Ochameyame Friends
He's cute, but...
Ochameyame Friends Fukurin is out!
Cute
But maybe not just Ochame Friends
That's for sure!
I don't know... but I don't know what kind of friends we're going to get.
I don't know what Friends are coming out!
I don't know what Friends are coming out.
Oh! Yellow-green!
Ah! Mr. Orkel!
Wait, wait, wait.
Isn't that Dora? Isn't that Doraemon?
What's that? It's that...
It's a magnet.
A time machine magnet.
It's not a funny item.
It's a mischievous item.
Pacikpokian Animal Shoeve
Oh, it's sold out!
That's great.
There he is.
Oh! That's a long time!
That's what I'm talking about, crispy.
That's great!
You can do it backstage.
What's that sound? I was like, "What's that?
It's like a lick.
Little old uncle.
Let's try this.
Can I try it? Here.
Oh, I got a channel subscription and an uncle.
Subscribe and an uncle.
Oh, I know you, I know you. I've seen it.
Is it Sakurazaka's YouTube?
I think so.
Buddies.
Buddy's just subscribed to the channel like this.
I got a Buddy's, and now I got one.
We got one.
Hoppe-chan.
It's Hoppo.
Hoppe.
Tea-me-phrase.
There's a tea-me-phrase.
What's your name?
I'm Pukurin.
I'm a little girl.
You're here?
Here, here, here.
I thought you'd like this masking tape.
Where?
Oni no Neme?
I like Mr. Unui.
Oh, you mentioned that.
This is nice.Okay, this one.
Topmost.
It's right here.
You know what?
It's this high.
This high.
Then put some money in it, please.
Money? I don't like it.
In here?
Come on.
I can't.
It's just impossible.
There's only a few more inches to go.
It's just a vine.
What an embarrassment.
Yo.
Well, excuse me.
Okay.
Here we go. Mr. Yuzuru.
Please.
Thank you, Mr. Uzui.
What is it?
Mr. Uzui's here.
Oh, look.
It's Mr. Uzui from the beginning.
So cool.
Wow, all kinds of colors are coming out.
I like it, too.
Wow, it's something.
It's cute. Look, it's cute.
I like blue, so blue now.
Blue.
Ta-da!
Oh, nice.
It's so big.
It's cute.
Oh, it's a kawasegami.
It looks like this.
It's a kawasemi.
You know, there was a mysterious one, right?
This was a 200 yen version of that.
I was a little curious about it.
I'm still a little curious about it.
Oh, you're curious?
Yeah, I'm curious.
I'll go.
Please do.
Here you go.
What is it?
It's very sturdy.
I got it!
Oh, what is it?
Something came out.
It's a real ball.
The true nature of the mystery gacha.
How was it?
It was a lot of fun.
A lot.
Isn't this amazing? This is it.
Today's MVP is Ochume Friends.
Fukubayashi-san.
Congratulations!
I had a great time and I want to come back again.
I want to come again.
Please try it, everyone.
Do you want to say that at the end?
Say that?
Great.
Channel subscriptions, high ratings, and good buttons.
High ratings and good buttons.
Please subscribe and rate my channel.
I'm new to YouTube, so I'll do my best.
Let's go Sumit.
Let's go.
Midori's place.
I read this.
Read it! Read it! Read it!Read! Read! Read!
Oh!
Great, great, great, great.
I got it!
Yay!
I didn't think I could do it in one shot.
I'm so happy!
Please subscribe to my channel!